{ "question": "reserva", "wrong_answer_1":'table', "right_answer":'reservation', "wrong_answer_2":'dish'}
{ "question": "mesa", "wrong_answer_1":'breakfast', "right_answer":'table', "wrong_answer_2":'waitre'}
{ "question": "vinho", "wrong_answer_1":'restroom', "right_answer":'wine', "wrong_answer_2":'menu'}
{ "question": "prato", "wrong_answer_1":'water', "right_answer":'dish', "wrong_answer_2":'silverware'}
{ "question": "café da manhã", "wrong_answer_1":'dinner', "right_answer":'breakfast', "wrong_answer_2":'lunch'}
{ "question": "banheiro", "wrong_answer_1":'drinks', "right_answer":'restroom', "wrong_answer_2":'table'}
{ "question": "garçon", "wrong_answer_1":'menu', "right_answer":'waitre', "wrong_answer_2":'dinner'}
{ "question": "jantar", "wrong_answer_1":'silverware', "right_answer":'dinner', "wrong_answer_2":'drinks'}
{ "question": "bebidas", "wrong_answer_1":'plates', "right_answer":'drinks', "wrong_answer_2":'cards'}
{ "question": "talher", "wrong_answer_1":'card', "right_answer":'silverware', "wrong_answer_2":'plate'}
{ "question": "cartão", "wrong_answer_1":'table', "right_answer":'card', "wrong_answer_2":'lunch'}
{ "question": "pedir", "wrong_answer_1":'chair', "right_answer":'order', "wrong_answer_2":'spoon'}


    
      